So I says, "Supercollider?
I just met her."
And then they built the supercollider.
Thank you. You've been a great audience.
Humorbot 5.0, ladies and gentlemen.
Our next stand-up's a veteran
of four comedy traffic schools.
Give it way up for Bobcat Zoidberg!
All right!
Earth. What a planet.
On Earth, you enjoy eating a tasty clam.
On my planet,
clams enjoy eating a tasty you.
Maybe I'm not yelling loud enough.
On Earth, everybody is always
looking for a giant squid.
On my planet...
Reload.
So these three parasitic worms
bore into a human's head...
...and they walk up to the bar
and then...
Uh-oh. Wait! Stop! I've got more!
My whole life I worked on that act,
and they hated it.
You're a crazy, penniless lobster doctor.
No combination of you
should be a comedian.
But comedy is in my valves.
My Uncle Harold was a big Hollywood star
back in the era of silent holograms.
Your uncle was Harold Zoid?
This I cannot deny.
Why, I've been a Harold Zoid fan
since back when my hips were made of bone.
As it happens, I still have
some of my original 78s.
You're right, crabby.
He's a hell of a lot funnier
than you could ever be.
Maybe so, but perhaps if I wrote him
and asked for a few hundred pointers...
This letter has to be very personal,
so I'm writing it in my own ink.
Dear Uncle Zoid, greetings
from your long-lost nephew.
Norm and Sam and Sadie's boy?
Remember?
Now I am the most important doctor
at the delivery company where I work.
But sadly,
my life is bereft of laughter.
"I beg of you, Mr. Funny Uncle.
Teach me the comedy business.
"Sincerely, Zoidberg."
Oh, isn't that nice he took the time?
What's that scribble-di-gook?
This is a fan letter
from my rich doctor nephew,
who just might be my ticket
out of this flophouse, he might.
Yeah, you'd better run.
Dear rich doctor nephew,
I can help you be funny.
The first funny thing you must do
is put all your money
in the form of a cashier's check
and come to Hollywood.
"Sincerely, Harold Zoid.
P.S. Cashier's check."
Did you hear that?
I'm going to Hollywood!
Welcome to Hollywood.
I must warn you,
there's no refund if you get discovered
and leave the tour.
I'm just kidding.
That never happens.
Now, to your right,
you'll see 30th Century Fox studios.
Fox uses those searchlights
to blind pilots,
then film the resulting plane crashes.
Neat.
Ahead, you'll see the home of Mel Gibson,
star of the hit film Bravehead.
And do we have any fans of Calculon,
star of the robot soap opera
All My Circuits?
Oh! I am! Me! Bender is!
Then you'll wanna get a close look
at his luxurious Bel Air home.
Yes, I will. Yep!
- Are you my new hot water heater?
- No, I'm Bender.
- We met once. Remember?
- Absolutely not.
Come on. Don't you remember
how much I was bugging you?
'Cause it was a lot.
- You remember, right?
- Look, I'm programmed to be very busy.
Unless you can heat water to 212 degrees,
I'm not interested.
Have you got
an extra "goto 10" line?
I said I don't need a Bender.
Bender? That was the other guy.
My name's Boiler.
Nice work, Boiler.
Thanks. And call me Bender.
That's where I'm meeting Uncle Zoid
for lunch
to discuss my Hollywood dreams.
Next time you see me,
don't be surprised if I've eaten.
Uncle Zoid, you're looking young enough
to be thrown back.
Rich nephew! Come over here
and give your uncle
a nice, big meal.
So, here we are,
a still-famous film comedian...
And a rich, respected doctor
with many surviving patients.
Eating real food in a restaurant,
as we both often do.
So, you want to be a comedian, is it?
It's my lifelong dream.
Well, that dream dies now!
You're unfunny and untalented!
That's why you're perfect for drama.
Hmm... Serious drama.
Perhaps it is time
to give up comedy.
I'm putting together a big drama picture
right now as we speak.
The script is dynamite.
I know, because I wrote it myself.
And with me directing and starring,
I'll be back on top
after 50 miserable years...
of fame.
Ah, fame. Where do I come in?
This fame film has a juicy part for you
if you completely finance it
with your doctor money.
So, are you in?
Uh... Okay.
How much do I have to invest?
Oh, not much. Not much. A million dollars.
Then it's settled.
Another blockbuster Hollywood deal.
What can I get you gentlemen?
Is bread free?
- Yeah.
- We'll split an order.
What's with Monstro?
He promised he'd give his Uncle Zoid
a million bucks to make a movie.
I've only been here a day,
and already I'm a Hollywood phony.
Perhaps I could call on
TV's Calculon to help,
now that I'm in showbiz.
- Since when have you been in the biz?
- Long enough, little man.
Long enough.
Calculon, as your hot water heater,
I would be remiss
if I didn't bring you scripts that could
make you an international film star.
Of course. Tell me about the project.
It's a movie.
Interesting. Tell me more.
Get this.
For a scant one-million-dollar investment,
you can be the star.
And?
And, I guarantee it'll win you an Oscar.
An Oscar, you say?
That would get me out of this
festering rat's nest called television
once and for all.
Let me see the script.
No. No, I don't like the font. Wait!
Harold Zoid?
Was this written by the Harold Zoid?
Written and xeroxed.
Good heavens.
A chance to work
with the legendary Harold Zoid.
He's one of my great idols.
And you say you can
guarantee me the Oscar?
I can guarantee you anything you want.
- Then I'll do it!
- Hooray!
Here's your checkbook.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you our director,
the legendary Harold Zoid.
Thank you.
A more classic movie plot there isn't.
A son who does not want to follow
in his father's business,
and that business
is being president of Earth no less.
The son, as it happens,
is vice president.
That plot makes perfect sense,
wink, wink.
Bender, you said "wink, wink" out loud.
No, I didn't. Raise middle finger.
Now, remember,
and I can't stress this enough,
this is a talkie,
so I want the full gamut of emotions
from every actor in every scene.
The Magnificent Three.
Scene one, take one.
And action!
Take back your gilded pen, Father.
Signing bills into law
was always your dream, not mine.
Cut! Cut! Cut it!
I said this is a talkie, damn it!
You've got to emote more!
And you extras.
Wave your arms and make faces.
What is this? A morgue?
The Magnificent Three.
Scene 10, take 95.
Action! And I mean
circus-grade action.
Sir, I call upon you
not as a president,
but as a father!
Cut! Cut! Cut it!
Would you show a little emotion?
People, people, please.
Just because it's a dramatic scene
doesn't mean you can't
do a little comedy in the background.
Throw a pie or two,
for God's sake.
No!
Cut! Cut it! Yuck!
Look. It's all right, kid.
We'll get it in editing.
All right. That's a wrap, everybody.
I'm gonna see you all at the premiere,
which, by the way, when is?
Well, editing is a long
and expensive process,
but we spent all the money on pies,
so it'll be ready Friday.
Nice turnout, Calculon.
That Oscar is practically on your mantle.
I just pray they like me
half as much as I do.
I agreed to be your vice president,
but I never agreed to be your son.
Thank you, Lieutenant Smith.
Good morning,
Mr. Vice President.
Leela, we're missing the premiere.
My only goal in life
is to attend a Hollywood shindig.
Just pay the valet the two bucks.
No. It's the principle of the thing.
Besides, I think I see a parking lot
up ahead.
Father, I have asked you
to join meon the White House roof
so we could have
a heart-to-heart talk.
I will never follow
in your footsteps.
Here is my resignation
as vice president.
No! My son will not
shame me like this.
I would sooner die,
I would.
Father! The ledge!
Oh...
The president is dead.
Congratulations, Mr. President.
No!
Woo-hoo! Yeah! He's a visionary!
Everyone walked out. They hated it.
I've seen plagues that had
better opening nights than this.
You said that Oscar was practically
on my mantle.
Now you know why I used the qualifier
"practically."
You listen to me.
I'm out a million bucks here.
You get me that Oscar or you're dead,
you and these sniveling lobsters!
Dead! You hear me? Dead!
Oy! Now he emotes!
400 categories,
and not a single nomination for me.
But you won this Golden Globe.
Piffle! That's the Emmy of movie awards!
I told you I want an Oscar!
Then maybe you should act better.
The Oscar isn't about acting,
it's about earning the respect
and admiration of the creative community.
How about we rig the awards?
That's fine too.
It's no use. The tar is too thick.
Plus, I think I flooded it.
Well, we missed the premiere,
and we're gonna die.
Might as well enjoy the sights.
Oh, my God. Sylvester Stallone!
This is where you live?
I thought you were
a big-shot Hollywood movie star.
No, I'm not.
I am an even bigger liar than you.
My career went down the tubes
the day they invented Smell-A-Vision.
Calculon's gonna kill us for sure,
and it's all everybody else's fault.
All I wanted was for people
to think of me one last time before I die.
What are you talking about, Uncle?
Everybody remembers Harold Zoid.
As a pathetic has-been,
they remember me.
- As a forgotten relic, they remember me.
- It's better to die now.
No! This is one death
Dr. Zoidberg won't be responsible for.
Zoidberg away!
Hi. I'm Joan Rivers's head.
I tell you, I've had so many face-lifts,
they finally lifted it
right off my body.
It's true! It's true!
Oh, oh, oh! Here comes Jack Nicholson's
DNA reconstituted in a gorilla body.
Catering.
Oh. Ugh...
Oh! And here's washed-up actor
what's-his-name, Harold Zoid.
Are you presenting one of those
tacky honorary awards or just getting one?
I'm a seat filler, Joan's head.
My only marketable skill
is to occupy space.
You know, the second I don't win
that award,
you're cat food.
Right, Boxy?
And now, the host
of the 1,074th Academy Awards,
Billy Crystal!
Now I know how a PEZ dispenser feels.
Oh, you like that one, Jack?
All right. We're already one hour behind.
Our first award tonight,
best cinematography
in a non-visible spectrum.
It's been two weeks.
You wanna play tic-tac-toe again
before we eat our shoes?
No. I always knew
I'd die at the bottom of a pit.
But a pit full of tar?
What was that?
A tar dolphin or a tar shark?
It's some kind of hollow tube
devoid of human life.
The Los Angeles subway!
We can blast our way in and escape!
All right, but I still feel like
having a shoe.
What category are they on?
They're giving out
the minor technical awards.
I think they're up to writing.
That just leaves
best soft drink product placement
and then best actor.
We don't have much time.
And the nominees for
best soft drink product placement are...
The Pepsi Generation.
They Call Me Mr. Pibb.
And Snow White
and the 7 UPs.
And now, to present the award
for best actor,
a bit player in the flop movie,
The Magnificent Three, Dr. Zoidberg!
Okay, Boxy.
Keep your prong on the trigger.
And the nominees
for best actor are...
Sir Laurence
in The Merchant of Venus.
Hive Mind Gamma 7-X
in Bikini Party Summer.
The Soda Machine Robot
Mark Jones
in How Beige Was My Jacket.
And instead of the fifth guy,
Calculon, for his powerhouse performance
in The Magnificent Three.
Uh-oh. He read the wrong name.
Shh! Just play along like they did
for Marisa Tomei.
Hooray! I won't be murdered!
I'll live another day.
Another day of pathetic, forgotten misery.
And the winner is...
And the winner,
instead of any of the nominees,
is the legendary Harold Zoid!
What?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You know, through all my ups and downs,
I always thought
the most important thing in life
was to win an Oscar.
But tonight I realize
what's really important
is to win two Oscars!
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
What really matters in life
is that people care about you,
whether it's a whole crowd...
...or just one diehard fan.
Aw!
Thank you, nephew.
Now I can die happy,
10 seconds from now
when Calculon kills us.
Harold Zoid!
Hit the deck!
Where's that Oscar?
Here. Enjoy. What are you getting upset?
It's slightly less fraudulent
for you to have it.
Yes. Yes, it's a real beauty.
Someday I hope
to win one of my own.
Then you're not gonna kill us,
Your Majesty?
Nay. I respect and admire Harold Zoid
too much
to beat him to death with his own Oscar.
Earthquake!
Hit the deck!
Let the Earth quake,
I've got somebody's Oscar!
We made it!
I'm at a Hollywood party.
I'm sorry, sir. This is a private...
Oh, pardon me.
I see you're with Mr. Stallone.